There were five days left for 14th August and today
we had to do some shopping for 14th August.
I quickly wore the burqa, took Basid Sahab and
my younger daughter along and left for the city
because all the shopping was
for my younger daughter.  The most frequently
asked question is which city do you
live in?  So this is the name of our beautiful city.  As soon as we
reached the city, shopping for 14th August
started.  First of all, the
suit is liked and measured to see if it is complete
or not.  After this, I liked tops and earrings.
After shopping on 14th August,
we again came to Aamir Bhai's shop because we had to
buy some things for home.  Finally, we bought some
tomatoes and onions, loaded the bike and headed back home
and on our return the weather was also amazing.  As soon as I
reached home, I opened all the stuff and
looked inside.  How did you all like our little 14th August
shopping?  I will tell you as per your wish.
See you in the next blog.  Allah Hafiz.